Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You don't say hello?
Félix! What the fuck?
Do you have your own key?
I might as well.
Everything yours is mine right now.
You know.
the reason I don't like to do favors.
is that some people see
compassion as weakness.
And then they think
they can take advantage.
That's not what this is.
I hope not.
Because I'm done with your bullshit.
It's not bullshit! I have the money.
If you had the money.
I would have the money.
right?
So tell me.
how is a housekeeper gonna
come up with 50 grand?
Well. 65 really.
That interest is a bitch.
I did it last time. didn't I?
Yeah.
I'm still kinda wondering about that.
I'll have it soon. Félix.
Okay?
I promise.
It's not that I don't believe you.
but I work better with deadlines.
You have till the end of the week.
That gonna be a problem?
Two weeks would be better.
That's a lot more interest.
Not if you cut me a break.
You want to cut me a break?
You know I always had a thing for you.
Sorry. Félix.
I just want to be friends.
Good night.
One week.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm